http://jobanimal.4jobs.com/policies/privacy

Privacy Policy
Please read the following policy so you understand how we use the personal information we ask you to submit. As we update and expand our services,
this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. If you use our Site (defined below) or any of our many offerings and services (the “Services”),
you confirm that you are not an individual in the European Union (EU) and agree to this policy.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us or write to us at Nexxt Inc., 676 East Swedesford Rd, Suite 300, Wayne, PA 19087.
Click on one of the following links to jump directly to that section:
Collection and Use of Information
Viewing and Updating Your Information
Cookies, Tracking, Interest Based Advertising, and Analytics
Cached Information
Log Files
Links
Security and Access
Children
California Residents
Do Not Track
Notification of Changes
Further Questions
Collection and Use of Information
When you register with this site or one of the web sites in our network (collectively, the "Nexxt Network" or the "Site"), we ask you for personal information,
such as your name, phone number, and email address. We use this information to process your requests, to communicate with you about the status of your requests,
and to review and improve the service we provide to you. At this time, we may subscribe you to various email publications. You can unsubscribe from any or all
publications at any time. We may also use your email address to send you information about your account, such as newsletters to which you are subscribed during
registration, as well as messages about any special offers, promotional announcements, and consumer surveys, Nexxt Services, account updates, services that may
be of interest to you, or administrative messages regarding your account. You can manage your email list options under your user account settings.
In addition, we may send job alert and other relevant text messages to your mobile phone number if you provide your mobile phone number and request these text
alerts when you register with our Site or update your account settings. Shortly after opting-in to this alert feature, you will receive a text welcome message.
You can opt-out of receiving these alerts by texting "STOP" to 34975. You understand and agree that you will receive a confirmation text that you have opted-out.
You also can manage whether to receive text alerts under your user account settings at any time. You understand and agree that if you opt-in to receive text alerts,
we also may text your mobile phone number on behalf of our clients and partners solely to send you job alerts and other relevant text messages.
We may also collect information about you automatically through your use of the Site.
This information may include:
Your activity on the Site, including the date and time of your visit, search terms you used, and content you accessed;
Your Internet Protocol (IP) address and general geographic area;
Your device identification and browser type; and
Information we collect through cookies, pixel tags, and other tracking technologies as described below in this policy.
By registering on or using our Site, you consent to the disclosure of your personal information to our partners and affiliates in accordance with your account
settings and this policy. Nexxt does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies, except with your express consent or
under the following limited circumstances:
We disclose information:
to companies and individuals we engage to perform services on our behalf;
to companies that may use your data for career-related purposes and other content that may be relevant to you;
if legally required to do so;
to protect the rights or property of the Nexxt Network or our affiliated companies, or
to protect the personal safety of users or the general public.
Additionally, information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership of our company.
In order to serve you better and more efficiently, we may also share anonymous aggregated information about users with our partners and other third parties.
We also offer an affiliate program, where affiliate members direct customers to the Nexxt Network through links on their Web sites. We ask affiliates for information,
including their site name (URL), mailing address, primary contact, pay-to address, technical contact, and other site-related information, to determine whether a site will
be included in our affiliate program. The information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for our affiliate program; none of this information is used for general
marketing purposes.
In some cases, our software and Site are utilized by our partners in a business alliance via their web community. In these cases, the information collected on our
Site is available to both companies.
You should be aware that any personal information (such as email address or resumes), which you voluntarily display or distribute on the Nexxt Network and/or on the
Internet can be collected and used by others, no different than posting this information in a newspaper. This may result in your receiving unsolicited messages from third
parties for which Nexxt is not responsible and has no ability to affect. If you click on a third party job posting and provide that party with your personal information,
we have no responsibility or control over that information.
At this time, we do not offer our Services to individuals in the EU.
Back to top
Viewing and Updating Your Information
You always have complete access to the information you have provided to the Nexxt Network. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime.
If you are a registered member, click here to access your account and manage your email options. We will delete data on our
Site that you have provided to us, upon request, through our Contact Us form.
Back to top
Cookies, Tracking, Interest Based Advertising, and Analytics
Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive and/or your mobile device. In general, we use
cookies and similar technologies to help us better serve you and improve your experience on our Site. As you browse areas of the Nexxt Network and view emails
from us, cookies may be placed on your computer's hard drive and/or your mobile device which may allow us to collect information, such as your internet protocol
address and mobile device identifier. Cookies allow us to track your account so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our Site. Cookies
also allow us to provide certain services and features to you. You may refuse cookies in your browser, but doing so may result in certain services and features
not functioning properly.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our Site. These advertisers may also serve cookies when
you click on advertisements on the Site, or use pixel tags, web beacons, or similar technologies, including within email advertisements we send on their behalf,
to collect non-personally identifiable aggregated information when users visit the Site in order to provide advertisements on our Site, other sites, and other
forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This common practice is known as "online behavioral advertising" or "interest based
advertising".
To learn more about this practice or to opt-out of this use of your information,
click here. In addition, if you
want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, you may visit each ad network's web site individually and opt-out. We do not have access to personal
information, if any, gathered by advertisers.
We also use the third-party analytics service Google Analytics to help analyze how users use our Site. The information generated by cookies or other tracking
technologies about your use of our Site is transmitted to Google Analytics, which uses such non-personally identifiable information to compile reports on user
activity. We may connect such information to other data that we have about the user.
Google Analytics’ ability to use and share this analytics information is
restricted by its terms of use and privacy policy. By using our Site, you consent to Google Analytics using your data in the manner and for the purposes described
above.
To learn more about how Google uses data, visit https://policies.google.com/privacy.
Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data company we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including on your
mobile device) to enable you to receive customized ads or content, including through online behavioral advertising. These cookies contain no personally
identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your
email address that we may share with a data company solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please
click here. Also, a data company, with or without the use of cookies and similar technologies, may use personal information
that we have collected or that you have provided online and link this information to IP addresses and/or device identifiers assigned to you as well as to
demographic and other data.
Back to top
Cached Information
There may be instances where information you have submitted to Nexxt is temporarily cached or stored by another site, such as Google.com, even after such
information has been removed from the Nexxt Network. These sites are maintained by third parties not controlled by Nexxt.
Accordingly, Nexxt expressly
disclaims any responsibility for the cached information displayed by these third-party web sites.
Back to top
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP
addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Back to top
Links
The Nexxt Network contains links to other sites. You may have arrived at this website by clicking on a link from a Nexxt affiliate or other affiliate.
If so, you should be aware that Nexxt may share your information with that affiliate and the affiliate may use the information in accordance with its
privacy policy instead of ours.
Back to top
Security and Access
We have implemented technology and security features, as well as internal guidelines, designed to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from
unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to endeavor to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. However, no data
transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and
you do so at your own risk.
When you place an order online at the Nexxt Network, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer
("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. This Site uses a service company
to process its credit card transactions.
Users should not post personal information to any site if they are uncomfortable with the security of the site. If you have any questions, please contact us.
Back to top
Children
This Site is not intended for, directed to, or designed to attract, children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly or specifically collect information
about children. This Site does not and will not contact children under age 13. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out
personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of this Site, we encourage you to use web-filtering technology to supervise your child's
access to the Site.
Back to top
California Residents
California law permits California residents to request and receive certain information about disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and a user of the Site and wish to request this information, please contact us or write to us at Nexxt, Inc., 676 East Swedesford Rd, Suite 300, Wayne, PA 19087, Attention: Customer Service. You may request this information once a year, and there is no charge for the request.
If you are a California resident, please refer to our California Privacy Policy for additional information regarding your privacy rights.
Back to top
Do Not Track
This Site does not include Do Not Track technology at this time. Do Not Track is a privacy preference that you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do
not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across web sites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For all the details,
including how to activate Do Not Track, visit www.donottrack.us.
Back to top
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under
what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Back to top
Further Questions
If you need information about Nexxt's privacy policy not stated above, use our Contact Us form or email us at privacy@nexxt.com.
© 2001 - 2020 Nexxt, Inc.Nexxt Patented Technology 4.0.2564.20496
